learnnext.com 2017-06-11

# CBSE TuTorial's Online, CBSE Maths, CBSE Science -Class X, Class IX, Class VIII , Class VII, Class VI

By using our Web site, you agree to comply with our policies. Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.

## What Information Do we Collect?

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site usage information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse/use our Web site.

## Personal Information You Choose to Provide

## Registration Information.

You will provide us information about yourself that will enable us to verify whether you are entitled to access and use certain information, materials and services available from the Web site LearnNext This information may also be used to enable us to enhance your Site visit, to assist you with customer service or technical support issues, or to follow up with you after your visit, or to otherwise support your relationship with [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) It is completely optional for you to participate. However, failure to participate may mean that you cannot access and use certain information, materials and services.  
For example, we request information from you when you:

  * Log-on to certain areas of the Web site LearnNext where you may be prompted to provide us with your Log in Name and Password as a condition to gaining access to certain information, materials or services.
  * Register or sign-up to use a service.
  * Subscribe to a newsletter or desire to be added to our mailing lists for other products and services.
  * Place an order.
  * Provide feedback in an online survey.

In each of the instances above, we typically ask for your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, Log in Name and Password, as well as, other similar personal information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers. On occasion, we may ask for additional information to enable us to provide you with access to and use of certain information, materials and services. In the case of newsletters or mailing lists, you will be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailers at any time.

Wherever [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

You undertake to not provide any false personal information on or create an account for anyone other than yourself without permission and keep your contact information accurate and up-to-date.

## How we use information

[Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) uses your personal information for specific purposes only. The personal information you provide to us when using the Web site, such as your name, postal, e-mail address or telephone number will be kept confidential and used to support your relationship with [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) to notify you of special offers, updated information and new products and services from [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/), or offers from third parties that we think may be of interest to you. Agents or contractors of [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) who are given access to your personal information will be required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for LearnNext.

## Sharing information with Third Parties

[Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) may enhance or merge your information collected at its Web site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you. With respect to network advertising companies (companies that manage and provide advertising for numerous unrelated companies), to the extent that [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) utilizes such advertising companies to provide advertisements on the Web site, may provide them with your Sign in Name and any demographic information about you that we collect. Those advertising companies may combine that data with non-personally identifiable data collected by the advertising company from your computer, solely for the purpose of delivering on our Web site, advertisements that are targeted to you.

Circumstances may arise where we are required to disclose your personal information to third parties for purposes other than to support your customer relationship with [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/), such as in connection with a corporate divestiture or dissolution where we sell all or a portion of our business or assets (including our associated customer lists containing your personal information), or if disclosure is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings.

We will send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Only [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) (or agents or contractors working on behalf of [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings.

## Cookies

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

Use of cookies makes web surfing easier by performing certain functions such as saving your Passwords, your personal preferences regarding your use of the particular Web site and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our Site will not function properly. You may note additionally that if you visit LearnNext Web site where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies. Advertisers and partners may also use cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

## Google Analytics cookies.

Google Analytics is software that lets us analyse how visitors use our site. We use this information to improve our website and provide the best experience to visitors.

These cookies collect data in an anonymous form. Please see Google's [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) for further information

Click here to opt-out of Google Analytics 

## How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. This Site does not, however, provide facilities for the secure transmission of information across the Internet. You should be aware that there are inherent risks associated with the transmissions of Personal Information via the Internet.

If you do not wish to use the Internet to transmit personal information you can mail or phone us, Details are provided under 'How to Contact us'.

## How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by calling LearnNext.

## Certain Disclosures

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or affiliated parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our site, the users of our site, and/or our affiliated parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our site, us, or third parties.

## What About Other Web sites Linked to Our Web site?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

## Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children below the age of 15. If we learn that we have personal information on a child below the age of 15, we will delete that information from our systems. Even for personal information of children of the age of 15 years and above, the personal information is collected only for the purpose of their educational requirement and service needs as provided by this Web site.

## Spamming

Sending unsolicited mail messages, including, without limitation, commercial advertising and informational announcements, is expressly prohibited. A user shall not use another site's mail server to relay mail without the express permission of the site.

It is contrary to [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) policy for customers to use our servers to effect or participate in any of the following activities:

  * To post to any Usenet or other newsgroup, forum, e-mail mailing list or other similar group or list articles which are off-topic according to the agreement or other owner-published FAQ or description of the group or list;
  * To send unsolicited mass e-mailings, if such unsolicited e-mailings provoke complaints from the recipients;
  * To engage in any of the foregoing activities using the service of another provider, but channeling such activities through [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) provided server, or using [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) provided server as a maildrop for responses;
  * To falsify user information provided to [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) or to other users of the service in connection with use of [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) service.. 

## Consequences of Violation:

When [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) becomes aware of an alleged violation of its Acceptable Use Policy, [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) will initiate an investigation. During the investigation [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) may restrict Customer 's access in order to prevent further possible unauthorised activity. Depending on the severity of the violation, [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) may, at its sole discretion, restrict, suspend, or terminate Customer's account and pursue other civil remedies. If such violation is a criminal offence, [Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) will notify the appropriate law enforcement department of such violation.

## Your Consent

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## How to contact us

If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, Please contact us at :

## Address

LearnNext  
Sri Nilaya Cyber Spazio,  
8-2-269/A/2/1-6, 1st floor, East Wing,  
Road # 2, Beside Annapurna Studios  
Banjara Hills,  
Hyderabad - 500033. 

## Revisions to this policy:

[Next Education](http://www.nexteducation.in/) reserves the right to revise, amend or modify this policy at any time and in any manner it pleases. Any change or revision will be posted on our Web site.
